本视频由哒哒字幕组原创译制
亲爱的主
Dear Lord,
请你保佑这个
blessed is the one  who reads aloud
大声朗读预言的人吧
the words of this prophecy.
尤金在这些照片的最中间
Eugene was in the middle of all of this.
快到时候了
BECKY: For the time is near.
就像你们知道的
As you all know,
在短短的四个月内
in just under four short months,
我们上市了阳光俱乐部
we're launching SunnyClub.
这是一个好兆头
BECKY: A great sign appeared.
这个脚踏月亮头顶太阳的女人
A woman cloaked in the sun  with the moon under her feet
这个头戴12星王冠的女人
and a crown of twelve stars  on her head.
她怀孕了
She was pregnant.
在她生下孩子的时候巨龙正窥探着她
And the dragon stood before thee as she gave birth.
霍华德
Howard!
但是他的孩子被上帝眷顾了
BECKY: But her child  was caught up to God.
我准备好了  我的主
I'm ready, my Lord.
然后这个女人向荒野逃去了
BECKY: And the woman fled  into the wilderness.
我们现在是百万富翁了
We're millionaires now.
但是至于杀人凶手
BECKY: But as  for the murderers...
我没管那个男的  让他独自死去了
I left a man to die alone.
- 奸诈者  - 我想在这里陪你的
-BECKY: Fornicators. -I wanna be there for you.
巫师
BECKY: Sorcerers.
- 原谅我  我必须要
-Forgive me, for I have s-- -
偶像大师
BECKY: Idolaters...
如果你为了尤金伤害到我
If you take me down for Eugene,
我会把你孩子带走
I will take your son with me.
至于所有说谎的人
BECKY: And all the liars...
我哥哥死的时候是我帮过他
I helped my brother die.
他们应当葬身于
BECKY: Their place  shall be in the lake
火海里
that burns with fire.
让那些不义之徒
Let the unrighteous...
我要结婚了
I'm getting married.
继续不义吧
BECKY: Continue  to be unrighteous.
让神圣继续神圣
And the holy  continue to be holy.
欢迎回家  孩子
Welcome home, son.
- 看好了  - 你好金杰
-BECKY: Behold. -Hello, Ginger.
我很快回来
BECKY: I am coming soon.
启示录22：12
Revelation 22:12.
以你的名字祈祷  阿门
In your name I pray, amen.
玛格丽特
JULIETTE: Margaret?
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doing in here?
我想我有点难过
Uh, I guess I'm kinda sad.
我是厨师的女儿
I'm the cook's daughter.
我永远都没法拥有楼下那些女孩所拥有的东西
I'll never have what those girls downstairs have.
跟我来
Come with me.
这是我的裙子
JULIETTE:  This was my dress
在我第一次亮相的时候穿的
when I first came out.
凭什么让富女孩都把乐趣夺走了呢
Why should rich girls have all the fun?
三  二  一
MARGARET: Three, two, one!
阳光俱乐部上线啦
And SunnyClub is live!
我的天哪
Oh, my goodness.
在这个特别的时刻
At this very moment,
令你的满意的产品
products that you  can feel good about
已经在来的路上了
are on their way to you.
没有你们的陪伴我们不会有今天
We couldn't have gotten here without you.
让我们花点时间
Let's take a moment
来铭记那些已经不在我们身边的人
to remember those who are no longer with us.
我们的牧师  保罗
Our reverend, Paul.
他是一个正直又令人尊敬的人
He was a truly honorable man.
当然了
And of course,
我们亲爱的尤金
our dear Eugene.
也许这时他正在天堂望着我们呢
May he be looking down on us from Heaven.
为上帝的所作所为感到骄傲
Be proud of what God has done.
上帝做的啥
What God has done.
我们应该为她开心
We should be happy for her.
阳光俱乐部  电视台
SunnyClub. Network.
贪婪
Greed.
那都是我过去生活的一部分
That's all just part of my past life.
要小心  不可将善事行在人的面前
Beware of practicing your righteousness before men,
故意叫他们看见
to be noticed by them.
若是这样  就不能得你们天父的赏赐了
Otherwise, you have no reward with your father.
安东尼奥和杰森和她在一起
Antonio and Jason were up there with her.
你也应该过去的
You should have been too.
现在是马克了
Mm, it's Mark now.
不管怎么说
Somehow, boys
几个月前那些
who couldn't even calculate a percentage
甚至无法计算蒙罗无限百分比的男孩子们
of Monroe Unlimited a few months ago
如今都有了自己的股份
ended up with ownership stakes.
金钱摧毁了人们  我很高兴自己摆脱了它
Money ruins people. I'm happy to be rid of it.
好吧  如果是这样
TINA: Well, if that's the case,
我就可以有25年的无偿子女抚养费了
there's 25 years of unpaid child support I could use.
让我们说几句话  爸爸
Um, give us a second, Daddy.
别和他计较太多
Take it easy on him.
尤金养活着埃里克和萝丝
Eugene provided for Eric and Rose.
现在  安东尼奥和马克拥有他一半的公司了
Now Antonio and Mark own half his company.
你拿到了什么
What did you get?
我以为你爱他
I thought you loved him.
这些年我一直都不清醒
All the years I was drunk.
他选择了回归咱们的家庭
He chose to come home to us.
我们需要留住他
And we're gonna keep him with us.
至少要再留几天
At least for another couple of days.
我还是不理解
I still don't understand why
为什么你要护着玛格丽特和萝丝
you're protecting Margaret and Rose.
我在乎他们
I care about them.
把这些在前厅摆成一条线
MARGARET:  Those line the foyer.
我需要每五英尺放一盆
And I want one every five feet.
嘿你们俩  能不能等会再卿卿我我
Hey, you two. You save that for later.
她还在适应
She's still getting used to the idea
我们实际上不是亲戚关系这个事儿
that we're not actually related.
现在你上楼把你自己打扮的好看点
Now you go upstairs and you make yourself gorgeous.
一切尽在我的掌握
I have things under control.
我真的很感激你对这些事情都这么洒脱
I really appreciate how cool you've been about everything.
实际上  我还在习惯
Well, to be honest, I'm still getting used to the idea
翻译：Evelyn
我的女儿嫁给了一个骗子
of my daughter marrying a fraud.
但是我们承受不起另一个丑闻了  对吗  小可爱
But we can't afford another scandal, can we, sweetie?
我与骗子的相处经验来说
And my experience with liars
你永远都不会知道最糟糕的情况
is that you'll never get to know the worst.
翻译：廿八
除此以外  我的萝丝爱你
Besides, my Rosy loves you.
我也爱她
And I love her.
你最好别干啥出格的事儿
You stay in line,
否则我会立即把你扔到监狱去
or I will haul you off to jail at a moment's notice.
翻译：二师姐
没有什么可以破坏我女儿完美的婚礼
Nothing is going to ruin my daughter's perfect wedding day.
即使是她的新郎
Not even her groom.
富 贵 逼 人
我这星期打了三轮高尔夫球
I've played three rounds of golf this week,
我今天早上要去大岛
and I'm going down to Grand Isle in the morning
去看一个房子
to look at a house.
你要去沙滩上
You on a beach?
校对：一江春水向西流
五英亩的海滩
Five acres of beach.
我从来没没见过你脱下过西装和领带
I've never seen you out of a suit and tie before.
统筹：折木奉太郎
你这个工作狂
You're a workaholic.
好吧  以后都不是了
Well, not anymore.
上市阳光俱乐部
Launching SunnyClub has set me up
总监：一芹
能让我四五辈子衣食无忧了
for four or five lifetimes.
接下来我准备坐好数钱了
I'm just gonna sit back and cash checks.
你和玛格丽特发生了什么
What happened to you and Margaret?
我一直计划提早退休
I always planned to retire early.
为什么  她说了什么关于我的事吗
Why? Has she said anything about me?
主啊  你们上床了
Lord, y'all had sex?
玛格丽特和我确实有些越界
Margaret and I crossed some lines with each other
做了一些我们彼此不应该做的事儿
that should not have been crossed.
好吧
Well...
美国最有权势的基督教妇女
the most powerful Christian woman in America
正接到华盛顿每位游说者的电话
is getting calls from every lobbyist in Washington.
华尔街的秃鹰们都在争取她让她走入公众视野
Wall Street vultures are wooing her to go public.
她需要你
She needs you.
这个女的不需要任何人
That woman doesn't need anybody.
作为我们的新董事会
As our new board of directors
你们将承担重要的责任
you'll have important responsibilities.
安东尼奥
Antonio, I would like you
我希望你去监督每一条点赞的评论
to oversee Praise-Per-View.
马克  你要经营欺诈部门
And Mark, you're going to run the fraud division
因为  这里需要一个懂欺诈的人
because, well, it takes one to know one.
富兰克林同意你安排的这个新的董事会吗
Did Franklin okay this new board of yours?
富兰克林走了
Franklin has moved on.
什么时候  为什么
When? Why?
伙计们  失陪了
Boys, would you excuse us?
我们需要富兰克林  知道吗
We need Franklin, okay?
因为安东尼娅  无论他他妈叫什么名字
'Cause Antonia and whatever the hell his name is,
他们都一点也不了解我们的业务
they don't know the first thing about our business.
安东尼奥可以有所作为的  马克很快也可以的
Antonio can be managed, and soon Mark will be too.
你这场结婚安排的可太好了
I knew you were taking this marriage too well.
如果萝丝嫁给了马克
If Rose marries Mark,
他的百分之31的股份就仍然在这个家里
his 31% is still in the family.
老实说  我从来没想过这些
Honestly, I never thought about it like that.
呵  我从来没想过这些
Ah, "I never thought about it like that."
你有做过任何事会不向着自己的利益吗
Is there anything you can't turn to your advantage?
我已经对马克进行了尽职调查
I've done my due diligence on Mark.
我保护萝丝就像我保护你一样
I'm protecting Rose just like I protected you.
别了吧  妈妈
Oh, come on, Momma!
你觉得我喜欢这样是吗
Do you think I like any of this?
我一点都不清楚你在想什么了
I don't know what the hell you think anymore.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
我不得不包裹住她
BECKY:  I had to swaddle her.
她要用她那小巧的指甲把自己眼睛给扣出来了
She's gonna claw her eyes out with those tiny nails.
过来
Come here.
你睡一会儿就会感觉好多了
You'll feel better when you get some sleep.
在我闭上眼的时候
When I close my eyes, it's all I see.
我就会一直看见我哥哥的尸体
My brother's body.
全是血
All that blood.
什么样的禽兽
What kind of animal
才会让一个人那样的死去
leaves a man to die like that?
- 埃里克  - 嘘
-ROSE: Eric!  -ERIC: Sh-sh-sh.
服务怎么样
How's the service coming?
你终于可以用上你利伯缇大学的学位了
You can finally use your Liberty degree.
你是真的疯了才会这样做吧
You're truly crazy to do this.
埃里克  别太过分了
Eric, don't spoil this.
就因为你的婚姻
Just because your marriage
失败的一败涂地
is understandably going down the toilet.
而我却得到了妈妈的祝福
And I actually have momma's blessing.
妈妈这么装模作样只是为了
Momma's only going along with this charade
把韦罗妮卡的股份留在家族里
to keep Veronica's shares in the family.
她教我们是非对错
She taught us right from wrong
但是只是在合适的时候
but only when it's convenient.
等下  你要去哪
Wait. Where are you going?
别当一个贱人  埃里克
Don't be a little bitch, Eric!
我已经给了玛格丽特一些时间了
I gave Margaret her moment.
现在我认为对我来说是时候重新和我的家人联系了
Now I think it's time for me to reconnect with my family.
我的意思是  除了你和你母亲以外的
I mean, beyond you and your mother.
我理解
I understand.
不好意思  我得接一下电话
Excuse me. I've gotta take this.
是萝丝
It's Rose.
嗨  你在哪呢
ROSE :  Hey, where are you?
这像个心理病房一样
It's a pysch ward in here.
我需要一个正常的人
I need someone sane.
我在准备你的结婚礼物
I'm just dealing  with your wedding present.
结婚
Wedding?
一会儿见  我得走了
Um, I'll see you later. I gotta go.
婚礼
Wedding?
好吧
Okay.
萝丝今天要和
Rose is getting married...
马克
to Mark...
结婚
today.
你之前为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
如果你去了  大家就会将今天铭记成
'Cause if you show up, everyone will remember it
尤金 · 蒙罗死而复生的一天
as the day that Eugene Monreaux rose from the dead,
而非萝丝 · 蒙罗的结婚日
not the day that Rose Monreaux married--
应该是我陪她走过红毯
I should be walking her down the aisle.
你才说过不想引人注意
Remember what you said about attention.
我不能把这个秘密背负在身上
ERIC: I can't carry  this around with me.
负担太重了
The burden's too much.
我父母教育我成为正直的人
My parents raised me right.
他们是这么教的
They did.
遵循上帝法则  你会得到奖赏
Follow God's laws, you'll be rewarded.
违背上帝法则  你会被惩罚
Break God's laws, you will be punished.
那如果违背上帝法则但仍受到奖赏呢
What if you break God's laws, and you are still rewarded?
如果你会变得
Right? What if you get richer and richer
越来越富有呢
and richer and richer?
那什么都不重要了
Then nothing matters.
对吧  什么都不重要了
Right? Nothing matters.
我不能生活在上帝是个儿戏的世界里
I can't live in a world where God is a joke.
签了认罪书  他就不是儿戏
DETECTIVE: Sign the confession, and He won't be.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
天呐
Jeez.
我们本来要去找你的
We were going to pick you up,
不过谢谢你让我们少跑一趟
but thanks for saving us a trip.
老兄  你终于安定下来了  对吧
ANTONIO: So, bro, you're finally settling down, huh?
-  对  -  感觉如何
-Yeah. -How does it feel?
就像我脑子终于正常了
It's like my goofy mind is finally sane.
强烈推荐
I recommend it.
那次打架之后  肯定有不少女人找你
You must've been drowning in chicks after that fight.
没  没我喜欢的
Nah, there's somebody I like.
给你个建议  我们现在是有钱人了
Piece of advice, we're men of means now.
我很幸运  我在变富有之前认识的萝丝
I mean, I'm lucky. I met Rose before I was rich,
外面可是有大把拜金女
but there's a lot of gold diggers out there.
-  嘿  闪闪动人  -  嗨
-Oh, hey, Sparkles. -Hi!
怎么样
ANTONIO: What up?
我看见你们上电视了
So I saw you guys on TV.
你们在镜头里都非常  非常帅
You both looked very, very handsome.
玛格丽特拖我们上去的
MARK: Yeah, Margaret dragged us up there.
-  你那时候在哪儿  -  只有股东才能参加
-Where were you? -It was for shareholders only.
给你
Here you go.
致一直以来支持我们的金杰
To Ginger, who always had our backs.
以后也会继续支持
And still does.
你能想象出来假如我们接受第一笔钱然后就回家会怎样吗
Can you imagine if we just took that first deal and went home?
如果不是你  我们不会在这里
We wouldn't be here if it weren't for you.
坦白来说
Let's be honest.
如果不是因为你们生命中的女人们
If it weren't for the women in your lives,
维罗妮卡  约皮
Veronica, Yopi,
你们俩还是会破产
you two would still be broke.
致让这一切变成可能的女人们
So here's to the women who made it possible.
干杯
Cheers.
我想分她点我的股份
ANTONIO: I want to give her  some of my shares.
她真的聪明
She's really smart.
她也应该进入董事会
She should be on the board, too.
亲爱的  你不用因为富有而有负罪感
Sweetie, you don't have to feel guilty about being wealthy.
还会有别人进入到你的生活中
There's gonna be people coming into your life now,
只是他们会心怀不轨
and, well, they just don't have the best intentions.
金杰一直以来都替我着想
Ginger has always had my best interests at heart.
我也是啊
And so have I.
董事会维持原状
The board will stay exactly how it is.
该彩排了
Time for rehearsal, everyone!
我们真的要彩排这个吗
Do we really have to practice this?
我这辈子都在这些台阶上走上走下
I've been walking up and down these steps my whole life.
但不是在紧张且穿高跟鞋的情况下
Not in heels with nerves.
这很有挑战性  信我
It can be challenging. You trust me.
马克  你站这里
Mark, you stand right here.
伴娘  你在这儿
And Maid of Honor, you're gonna be here.
这里本该是埃里克
And here and I guess I'll be Eric
鉴于找不见他人  就由我替他
since, well, he's nowhere to be found.
我永远不会忘记
I will never forget the night that I descended that staircase
下楼和你们爸爸共舞的夜晚
to dance with your daddy.
那晚是我的成人礼舞会
It was the night of my debutante ball.
尤金  他在楼下等待
Eugene, he was waiting down below,
向我伸出手  看向我的表情
and he stretched out his hand to me
让我觉得我是他世界里唯一的女人
with a look that said I was the only woman in the world.
几个月后  我就成了尤金·蒙罗太太
A few months later, I became Mrs. Eugene Monreaux.
音乐停
Cut the strings.
你成人礼仅几个月后
GINGER: So you married Eugene a few months
就嫁给了尤金
after your debutante ball?
-  那时候他多大  -  我不知道
-How old was he? -Oh, well, I don't know.
23或24岁
23, 24.
此时非彼时
It was a different time.
我很荣幸被选中
And I was proud to be chosen.
我们接下来去哪儿
TINA: Where do we go from here?
我希望是天堂
Heaven, I hope.
我是说接下来你以什么为生  尤金
I mean where are you going to live, Eugene?
你打算重新收回
And are you planning to take back
电视台吗
your place at the network?
我从世俗财产中解脱了
I am free of earthly possessions.
你也许想让金杰和他们分担这些世俗
You may want to burden Ginger with them.
我正试图引领我的孩子走向光明
I am trying to guide my child into the light,
而你满脑子只有钱
and all you can talk about is money?
我不想让她重蹈覆辙
I don't want her to make my mistake.
25年了  你不能对此事避而不谈
You can't waltz in here after 25 years
还指望她像你一样思考
and expect her to think like you.
你说得对
You're right.
等等
Wait.
金杰不让你去的
Ginger said not to leave.
我得为我的女儿们做点好事
I need to do right by my daughters.
一直以来  你都是个警察
This whole time, you've been a cop.
其实我是联邦调查局的
FBI, actually.
如果你还活着  那就没有证据指控我
Well, well, if you're alive, then you got nothing on me.
有手写认罪书  谋杀未遂
Except a written confession. Attempted murder.
犯罪现场逃逸
Fleeing the scene of a crime.
这是诱捕  你策划好的
That's entrapment. You planned this.
不能因为你没有成功实施犯罪
Just because you weren't successful at committing
就说明没有犯罪
a crime doesn't mean there was no crime.
窃听器
A wire?
-  你疯了  -  直觉告诉我
-You're crazy. -You know, a hunch tells me
当你看到犯罪现场时
that when you looked at my crime board,
你就把注意力集中在你认识的人身上
you zeroed in on the people that you knew.
牧师  他的朋友  家庭
Reverend, his pals, family--
我姐夫死了
My brother-in-law's dead.
我的叔叔们都不做这行了
My uncles are out of the business.
那些是你认识的恶魔
Those were the devils that you knew.
而你不认识的恶魔  他们危险得多
The devils you don't know, they're far more dangerous.
1820团体没有结束
The 1820 isn't finished.
这些年来  它们变得越来越国际化
Over the years, they've grown increasingly international.
鉴于到你母亲的影响力
And in light of your mother's new position of influence,
他们会对她下手
they're gonna make a play for her.
我们得知道他们要什么
We need to know what they want.
你可以对我做你想做的
You can do what you want to me,
但我不会监视我的家人
but I'm not spying on my family.
你有24小时考虑
You got 24 hours to think it over.
为什么你不重新审视家人
Why don't you take a hard look at your family
扪心自问
and ask yourself,
他们值得让你的女儿在
"Are they worth that little girl growing up
没有爸爸陪伴的环境下长大吗
without her daddy?"
你还是把钥匙藏在假石头下面
You still hide your keys under that fake rock.
-  你是鬼吗  -  不是
-Are you a ghost? -EUGENE: No.
但我需要让你帮我死而复生
But I need you to make me alive again.
谢谢你帮玛格丽特穿上那条裙子
ELLIE: Thanks for fixing  Margaret up with that dress.
她永生都会铭记这一晚的
She'll remember this night for the rest of her life.
她好可爱
She is so lovely.
尤金先生已经过了适婚年龄
Mr. Eugene is past marrying age.
他要找到一个心仪他的姑娘
He needs a girl who adores him,
一个待他入王子般的
who will treat him like the prince he is,
有信仰的女人
a woman of faith.
箴言31 才德的妇人谁能得着呢
Proverbs 31, "A wife of noble character who can find
她的价值远胜过珍珠
she's worth far more than rubies."
我们都希望孩子们得到最好的  不是吗
We all want what's best for our children, don't we?
-  阿门  -  艾莉
-Amen to that. -Ellie!
莫妮克  富兰克林
ELLIE: Monique! Franklin!
坐下
JULIETTE: Sit. Sit down.
还有谁知道你还活着
FRANKLIN: Who else knows about you?
只有金杰
Just Ginger.
和缇娜
And Tina.
我不知道你在期待什么
Look, I don't know what you're expecting, Gene.
但你不能就这么走回家
But you're not just gonna stroll back home.
生活在继续  人们在改变
Life's moved on, people have changed,
阳光俱乐部已超出你我最疯狂的预期
SunnyClub launched beyond our wildest dreams without you.
但我需要你帮玛格丽特做好准备
But I need you to prepare Margaret.
让她别太震惊
For the shock?
还是说你想拿重回公司掌权
Or for you to try to take control of the company?
我的灵魂是纯净的  我已经放下世俗琐事
My soul is clean. I've given up worldly things.
但有些别的事我得做
But there is other business I need done.
我怕她会不高兴
I fear it might upset her.
为什么来找我
Why come to me?
因为你是我永远可以信赖的人
Because you're the one I could always count on.
我的天
MARGARET: Well, my goodness.
谁让你这么摆桌子的
Who taught you to set a table?
别妄加评论  我是吃叉子长大的
No judgments. I grew up eating off sporks.
你有没有给安东尼奥拉过小提琴
Did you play those violins for Antonio,
让他对自己的好运感到内疚
guilting him about his good fortune?
他的好运很大程度上要归功于我
His good fortune is in large part thanks to me.
我给过你公司股份  一份工作
I offered you a stake in our company, a job.
你不要
You walked away.
男孩们也没要
The boys walked away, too.
但他们却都在董事会占有一席之地
And yet somehow they're on the board
做那些他们没资格做的重大决定
making major decisions they're unqualified to make.
他们拥有唯一至关重要的资格
They have the only qualifications that matter.
-  性别  -  耳根子
-Testicles? -Ears.
他们听我的
They listen to me.
-  你从不听我的  -  我听过
-But you never have. -I have listened.
上周  我随时都可以
In the last week, I could've blown up SunnyClub
毁掉阳光俱乐部
any time I wanted.
但我没有  因为我在乎这个家庭
I didn't, because I care about this family.
这是又一次任性的虚张声势吗
Is this another one of those petulant bluffs?
我向你保证不是
I assure you it isn't.
你应该庆幸你在我们的餐桌上
You should just be grateful that you still have a seat
仍有一席之地  金杰
at our dinner table, Ginger.
因为你永远都不会坐进董事会中
Because you will never have a seat on our board.
上车  老家伙
Get in, old man.
-  卢克  -  嘘
-Luke? -Shh.
南方女人随时为结婚而准备
ROSE: Southern women  are groomed for marriage.
就像童话故事一样
It's like this whole fairytale thing.
事情本不应该是这样的
And this is not how any of it is supposed to go.
我没意见
And I am fine with it.
除了在种植园
Well, except for the part
结婚这部分
about getting married on a plantation,
你在打破南方传统这方面
I'd say you're doing a pretty good job
做得都很好
of breaking southern tradition.
是个营地
It's a camp.
亲  是个植物园
Honey, it's a plantation.
唯一让我伤心的就是
I think the only thing that I am really sad about
爸爸不在
is that Daddy isn't here.
杰森看到他了
Jason saw him.
杰森  我们真正的兄弟  不是我要嫁的那个
Jason, our actual brother, not the one I'm marrying.
他告诉马克  他失去意识后
He told Mark that when he was unconscious,
爸爸去找过他
Daddy came to him,
而且
and...
自从马克跟我说了这事后
ever since Mark told me that,
我一直在祈祷爸爸的灵魂也会来找我
I've been praying that Daddy's spirit would visit me, too.
祷告是很灵的
Prayer is powerful.
萝丝
Rose--
喂  富兰克林
Hey, Franklin.
你父亲来找过我了  你知道他活着
Your father came to see me. You knew he was alive.
- 是的  - 问问他来不来
-I did. -Ask him if he's coming.
你居然没告诉我  简直太蠢了  这个我们以后再说
We'll discuss the stupidity  of you not telling me later.
我明白
I understand.
让我跟他说
Let me talk to him.
喂  富兰克林  我知道你跟妈妈干过那事了
Hey, Franklin, I know that you and Momma did it.
那天晚上我在家  你俩好大声
I was in the house that night. You guys were totally loud.
我没意见的  听着  我爱你
I'm fine with it. Now, I love you.
我也爱你  孩子
I love you, too, kid.
你能来吗
Will you please come?
不行
I can't do that.
但祝你今天幸福美满  萝丝
But you have a beautiful day,  Rose.
美
Beautiful.
在新奥尔良想乖乖当死人可不容易
LUKE: Not easy to stay dead  in New Orleans.
当时你说想作证
When you said you wanted to testify,
我信了  我以为是在法庭上作证
I took you literally, as in court.
你能指认许多有权势的人
Powerful people you can help put away.
我会尽力
I will do my part.
听着  这很危险
Now, it's dangerous.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
但我们愿意给你提供证人保护服务
But we're prepared to offer you witness protection.
换个地方  换个身份
New location, new identity.
重新开始  你想要的不就是这个吗
Fresh start. Isn't that what you wanted?
牧师让我坠机的时候  其实是帮了我
Reverend did me a favor when he took my plane out of the sky.
让我看到了更高的人生目标
Made me see my higher purpose.
我不需要保护  我有上帝
I won't need protection. I have God.
你去哪儿  尤金
Where you going, Eugene?
我得赶去参加婚礼
I have a wedding to get to.
我们的  我们的誓言
We take our--we take our vows.
我们从  我们从
We take our wedding-- we take our wedding--
科林斯人那里学会婚礼誓言
We take our wedding vows from Corinthians.
13章  爱是耐心
Chapter 13. "Love is patient.
爱是仁慈
Love is kind."
才怪
Yeah, right.
它不粗鲁  不易怒
"It is not rude. It is not easily angered.
不记仇
Keeps no record of wrongs."
蕾切尔  嘿
Rachel, hey.
我能跟你说句话吗
Hey, can I talk to you?
保罗牧师的事我很难过
Hey, I'm so sorry about Reverend Paul.
你太太一定伤心欲绝
Your wife must be devastated.
- 嘿  - 我都不知道你会来呢
-Hey! -I didn't know you'd be here.
她在酒店里愁眉苦脸的
She was moping around the hotel.
我就把她当对象带来了
I brought her as my date.
- 你好吗  兄弟  - 嘿
-What's up, buddy? -Hey.
你们这对帅哥靓妹去给我们点两杯酒吧
Why don't you two cuties get us some drinks?
- 好  - 当然
-Yeah. -Sure.
如果你爱她
If you love her...
就放她继续生活
you'll let her move on.
这是你要穿去参加我和布雷特婚礼的衣服
That's the dress you were gonna wear to my wedding with Brett.
我们也许很有钱  但我很节俭
We may be rich, but I'm thrifty.
而且这衣服很漂亮
And besides, it's stunning.
不行  我不让你穿
No! I don't want you to wear it.
好吧
Fine.
我换一件
I will wear something else.
妈妈  看着我
Momma, look at me.
我知道你和富兰克林之间发生了什么
I know what happened between you and Franklin,
我可以接受
and I am okay with it.
而且  不管怎么说
And for what it's worth,
如果你想开始新生活
if you were to move on...
大家都会理解的
everyone would understand.
亲爱的  我能不能穿你设计的衣服去参加婚礼
Sweetie, can I wear one of your designs to the wedding?
我给啥你穿啥
No questions asked?
你给啥我穿啥
No questions asked.
空气中弥漫着爱情
MARGARET: Love is in the air.
你看到安东尼奥和蕾切尔讲话了吗
Did you see Antonio talking to Rachel?
妈呀  新娘的母亲怎么选了这么条裙子
Wowie, that's an interesting choice for Mother of the Bride.
身为父母
Ah, well, as a parent,
会明白牺牲的含义
you learn the meaning of sacrifice.
拜托  为了你妹妹  开心点
Please try to be festive for your sister.
贝琪要跟我离婚
Becky asked me for a divorce.
她出轨了
Cheated on me.
我们家就是这样
That's what we do in this family,
出轨成性
cheat on each other.
我知道这有多伤人  我懂的
I know how hurtful that is, I do.
你一直培养我们
You raised us...
去潇洒地生活
to live such a charmed life.
不留遗憾
Without any regrets.
但现在  我总是情不自禁地
But now, I can't help but find myself
一遍又一遍地重复
repeating over and over and over again...
早知今日  何必当初
If I had known then what I know now.
去拿冷水洗把脸
You go splash some cold water on your face,
别给你妹妹丢人
and you do your sister proud.
好的  妈妈
Okay, Mom.
嘿  瞌睡虫
Hey, Sleepy-head.
快开始了
It's about to start.
我做了个好奇怪的梦
I had the craziest dream.
我逃离了这一切
I ran away from all this.
听着  我现在家里有客人
Look, I have a house guest right now,
但他马上就走了
but he'll be leaving soon.
你可以过来跟我住
You can come stay with me.
是你
ERIC: It was you?
世上那么多人
Out of all the people in the world...
偏偏是你
it's you.
埃里克
Eric.
你不明白
You don't understand.
事情没那么简单
It's more complicated than that.
没那么简单
Complicated?
有其父必有其女
We're our father's children.
埃里克
Eric.
亲爱的  你可是首席伴娘
Sweetie, you're the Maid of Honor.
赶紧去现场吧
You best take your place.
萝丝
Rose?
进来
ROSE: Come in.
我的好女儿
Oh, my baby girl.
怎么样
Well...
你太美了
You are a vision.
我
I...
希望我不会让你伤心
I hope I'm not breaking your heart.
妈妈
Momma--
我们为了公事调查过马克
We had to vet Mark for the business,
本来我不想给你看的
and I was gonna keep this to myself.
不  不管这里面有什么  我都要嫁给马克
No, whatever's in that thing, I am marrying Mark.
我爱他
I love him.
我只是不想你以后变成我  亲爱的
I just don't want you to be me, Sweetie.
我知道你有多爱他
I know how much you love him.
但我希望你在进入这段婚姻时
But I want you to go into this marriage...
是客观清醒的
with both eyes open.
我很抱歉  埃里克
I'm so sorry, Eric.
我老婆在和我妹妹上床
My wife is sleeping with my sister,
而我弟弟在勾搭我女朋友
and my brother is hitting on my girlfriend.
没人比我惨了吧
I think I'm the sorry one.
各位  请回吧
Everyone, please go home!
- 小萝  - 就当你从没认识过我
-Ro? -Pretend that you never knew me.
小萝
Ro--uh--
你杀了他两次  马克
You killed him twice, Mark.
你嗑药磕嗨了  撞了车
You were high and crashed the car.
他会陷入昏迷本来就是你害得
I mean, you put him in a coma in the first place.
我没撒谎
-I didn't lie. -
我老老实实地告诉了你一切
I told you everything from the heart.
只是没用同样的词
I just didn't use the words.
你说是安乐死
You said it was euthanasia.
是安乐死  我
It was. I...
不对  这是过失杀人
I mean, this is manslaughter.
那是在安乐死之前
It was before the euthanasia.
真相是很简单的  马克
The truth is simple, Mark.
你想要简单的真相吗
You want the simple truth?
我和你哥  我们是在街头卖大麻的
Me and your brother, we sold weed on the streets.
我们过着放肆的生活  有时候会出事
We lived crazy, and things happened.
那次车祸就属于出事了
And the crash was one of those things.
如果你想听
And if you want to hear about it...
我真的不想再听了
I really don't.
你说得对  我也不想
You're right. I don't, either.
这和我的世界太不同了
It's just so not my world.
对  我知道
Yeah, I knew that.
所以我才回了家
And that's why I went home.
又让你把我拽回来
Then I let you drag me back here.
我把自己的生命都交给了你
I trusted you with my life.
而且为此高兴
I'm glad that I did.
因为我爱你  萝丝
'Cause I love you, Rose.
是真爱
Real love.
别说了
Stop it.
基督徒不是能赎罪吗
I mean, don't Christians have redemptions?
我们离开这儿吧
We could just get out of here, you know?
去市政厅结婚  地方由你挑
We'll get married at city hall or wherever you want.
我知道  我们一定会幸福
I just--I know this can work.
我需要考虑一下我的生活  马克
I need to think about my life, Mark.
我能等
I can wait.
别等
Don't.
我完全没想到
I did not see that coming.
我以为他们很相爱
I thought they were in love.
爱没什么用
Love doesn't mean anything.
问问蕾切尔吧
Just ask Rachel.
她人呢
Where is she?
她跟我妈回家了
She went home with my mom.
免费看高清美剧韩剧日剧泰剧就上人人视频app，各大手机应用商店均可下载
你会上她吗
You gonna do her?
应该会吧
I think I will.
喂  你俩能不能别跟两个小娘们似的
Hey, can you guys stop being little bitches?
你们俩都去死吧
You can both go to hell.
彩虹骚货
Jank-ass rainbow girl.
住嘴
Stop it.
你知道你妈是妓女吗
Hey, you know your mother's a whore?
你是想打架吗
You want to go?
- 你是想打架吗  - 打吧
-You want to go? -Yeah, let's go.
- 住嘴  - 那天晚上
-Stop it. -And the fact--
你居然还能坐在那儿
what, you sat there the other night
一个劲地安慰我
trying to make me all feel better
让我别对出轨的事太难过
about cheating on my wife?
你应该对你老婆更好点
You should've pleased your wife a little bit better.
我说了对不起
I said I'm sorry.
如果我们俩伤害了你  那也是无心之失
If either of us hurt you, it was by accident.
无心之失  无心之失
Accidents, huh? Accidents.
不  你们才是无心之失
Nah, you are the accidents.
你和你  你们才是无心之失
You and you, you're the accident.
你们才是  你们才是无心之失
You're the accident. You're all the accidents.
埃里克  冷静点  否则你明天会后悔的
Eric, chill, or you're gonna regret this tomorrow.
我会后悔  我会后悔
Oh, I'm gonna regret this. I'm gonna regret this.
安东尼奥说我会后悔
Antonio said I'm gonna regret this.
- 没错  - 好吧
-Yeah, you are. -Okay!
- 我会有后悔的事  - 好了
-I'm gonna regret something. -Okay.
我会后悔什么呢  我会后悔这个吗
What am I gonna regret, buddy? Am I gonna regret this?
别闹了
Hey! Cut it out.
干嘛  后悔吗  你想来毁我
What, regret this? You came here to destroy me,
毁我啊  来啊
so destroy me. Come on, man.
哥们  别这样
Brother, you don't want to do this.
哥们
Brother?
别打了  有毛病吗
Hey, cut it out, man! What is your problem?
别别别
No, no, no, no.
住手啊
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
- 住手啊  - 怎么样
-Guys, stop it. -What's up, homie?
怎么样  干什么啊
Huh, what's up? What's up?
住手  安东尼奥
Stop it! Antonio!
别打了
Stop it! Hey!
- 住手啊  - 怎么样啊
-Just stop it! -Huh? What's good, homie?
- 杀了我吧  - 怎么样
-Just kill me! -What's good?
安东尼奥
GINGER: Antonio!
- 弄死我啊  - 不
-Kill me. -No.
- 弄死我  - 住手啊
-Kill me. -Stop it.
杀了我啊
-Kill me! -
住手
Son, stop!
大家都是家人  不要这样
Your brother's blood cries out to me form the ground.
住手吧
Now stop.
你干嘛来了
What are you doing here?
照顾好你兄弟
See to your brother.
天啊
Oh, my God.
起来
Hey, get up.
可能我没说清楚
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
你来这里干什么
You have no business here.
不是来找你的
I didn't come here for you.
我得做一件你不喜欢的事
I had to do something you won't like,
或者说你根本不会理解的事情
or even understand at first.
但我是为了保护家族产业
But I did it to protect the business.
我不用你保护
I don't need your protection.
我不需要任何人保护
I don't need anyone's.
要大乱了
Total chaos is coming.
玛格丽特
Margaret...
尤金还
-Eugene is-- -
萝丝
-Rose? -
Rose!
玛格丽特
Margaret.
尤金
Eugene.
尤金和他三个朋友打了我儿子
MONIQUE: Eugene and three of his friends jumped him.
我儿子浑身是血
Left my son in a pool of his own blood.
尤金不会的
Eugene wouldn't.
尤金会的
Eugene would.
我要正义
And I want justice!
别闹啊  莫妮克
What--no need to make a fuss, Monique.
尤金不会坐牢的  你知道的
Eugene will never go to jail. You know that.
如果这件事不说出去
If we keep this between us,
我会确保
I'll see to it that Franklin
富兰克林再也不用在这工作了
won't ever have to work in this house.
考虑下吧
Think about it.
我得回去招呼客人了
I have to get back to the party.
这是你的机会啊
This is your opportunity.
不会有比这再好的了
Can't do better than that.
你要让我扔掉我儿子的尊严吗
You want me to throw away my son's dignity?
这是机会吗
For an opportunity?
是  希望他们之后会感激我们吧
Yes. And hope they thank us for it later.
你跑哪去了
Where the hell have you been?
上帝让我踏上精神追求之旅了
God sent me on a spiritual quest,
一路崎岖回到了家
a crooked path that led me home.
这崎岖的一路上没有电话可以打吗
And there were no phones on this crooked path?
我是被你母亲
I was guided by your mother
我母亲  和富兰克林的母亲引领这回来的
and my mother and Franklin's mother and...
我还在科罗拉多复活了我儿子
then I resurrected my son in Colorado,
虽然很短暂吧
if only briefly.
你肯定累坏了
You must be exhausted.
死了都比我经历的一切要容易
Dying would've been easier than what I've been through.
你经历的一切
What you've been through?
你有脸说
Really?
你让你家人以为你都死了
You let your wife and children think you were dead,
我们捧在手心的一切原来都是一个谎言
while everything we held sacred turned out to be a lie.
你真不要脸
You're shameless.
你应该像一条两条腿的狗一样
You should be crawling to me
摇摇晃晃的爬向我
like a two-legged dog in a ditch.
富贵还真是让你逼人了  玛格丽特
Being rich makes you filthy, Margaret,
我曾经比你有钱的多得多
and I was very, very rich.
现在多亏了我  你更有钱了  尤金
And you're even richer now, Eugene, thanks to me.
我已经放弃了物质生活
I have given up material things.
但你还是穿着笔挺的燕尾服
Says the man in white tie and tails.
我是为了参加婚礼  尊重新娘
I'm dressed for a wedding out of respect for the bride.
他为什么要这么对我们
ERIC:  Why would he do that to us?
他病了
He's sick.
这一切都太变态了
It's all just so sick.
他干嘛就这么
I mean, why would he show up?
突然出现呢
Just out of the blue like this?
全家人都是疯子  我都不知道该咋说
This family is nuts. I don't even know what to say.
我求他再等一天的
I begged him to wait one more day.
就一天
Just one more,
让你和马克成为焦点的
and let it be about you and Mark.
什么叫你求他
What do you mean you begged him?
你知道我们的父亲还活着吗
You knew my father was alive?
你知道多久了
How long? How long you know?
不是很久  我就是
Not long at all. I was just--
天啊  我是他女儿啊
Oh, my God. I am his daughter!
我有权利知道的
I had a right to know!
我也是他女儿的
I'm his daughter, too.
你都拥有他几十年了  我就想要一点时间
You all had decades with him. I just wanted a little time.
我们都想的啊
We all would've wanted that.
- 闭嘴  - 他是我父亲
-Shut up. -He was my father.
对你来说   他只是贡献了精子
He was just your sperm donor.
再见吧
We're done.
你爱过我吗
MARGARET:  Was any of it ever love?
当然了
-EUGENE: Of course, it was. -
你是我的掌上明珠
You were my jewel, but we...
但我们的感情基础是财富和血泪
We were a love built on blood and treasure.
如果你不想掺和  你还来干什么
If you don't want our business, then why are you here?
来跟我的孩子们赎罪
I made amends to my sons.
我打开了埃里克的双眼
I opened Eric's eyes,
让他不至于这辈子就这么堕落下去
and I saved him from a life of corruption.
我从疯子手里救下来安东尼奥的孩子
I saved Antonio's son from the clutches of a madman.
我让杰森有了生命
I breathed life into Jason.
但我辜负了女儿们
But I have failed my girls.
我想牵着萝丝走过红毯
Now, I wanted to walk Rose down the aisle,
但我来的太迟了
but I'm too late.
我想要给金杰一个新的生活
I tried to make a new life for Ginger.
一个她以为她想要的生活  但是虽然你俩都不愿承认
A life she thought she wanted, but she is more like you
她其实跟你很像
than either of you are willing to admit.
于是我意识到  只有一件事
And I realized there was only one thing
可以满足她
that would satisfy her.
我在蒙罗无限公司的股权
My ownership stake in Monreaux Unlimited.
我没要他这样的  玛格丽特
No, I didn't ask him, Margaret.
我发誓
I swear.
但这是你想要的  亲爱的
But it is what you wanted, darling,
比什么都想要
more than anything.
所以现在你需要
And so now you will have to...
自己找寻救赎了
seek salvation on your own.
该你接受上帝的考验了
It's your turn to be tested by God.
你疯了
You're insane.
不  我很清醒
No, I am clear.
上帝救了我  让我为我的六个孩子
God saved me so that I may do right
能做出正确的事情
by all six of my children.
6个吗
Six?
尤金
BECKY: Eugene?
你回来找我们了
You came back for us.
我那时只是孩子啊
I was just a child.
我的孩子引领我回家了
My child has led me home.
你是个禽兽
You are a monster.
不
No.
我只是个谦卑的罪人
I am just a humble sinner.
一个重生的谦卑的罪人
A humble sinner born again.
你不许再踏进这个家一步
Never set foot in this house again.
生意可以给你  房子是我的
Y'all can have the business, but this house is mine.
这个珍贵的基石
It is the precious cornerstone
是我孩子新生活
of a sure foundation for my child,
坚实的基础
for a new life.
滚出去
Get out of this house.
全都给我滚出去
Everyone, out! Now!
* Pray God you can cope *
* I'll stand outside *
* This woman's work *
* This woman's world *
* Ooh, it's hard on a man *
* Now his part is over *
* Now starts the craft *
* Of the Father *
* I know you've got  a little life in you left *
* I know you've got  a lot of strength left *
* I should be crying *
* But I just  can't let it show *
* I should be hoping  but I can't stop thinking *
* Of all the things  we should've said *
* That I never said *
* All the things  we should have done *
* That we never did *
* All the things  we should have given *
* But I didn't *
* Oh, darling make it go *
* Make it go away *
父亲的罪孽
ERIC:  The sins of the father
不会变成孩子的罪孽
will not be  the sins of the son.
我父亲回来了
My father's returned,
我要不惜任何代价  保护我母亲
and I need to protect my mother at any cost.
找我就行了
I'm your guy.
给我装备上吧
Wire me up.
SINGER: * My love, child *
* I know you have a little  life in you yet *
* Whatever you need *
* I know you have a lot  of strength left *
* Give me your hand *
* I know you have a little  life in you yet *
* I know you have a lot  of strength left *
* Oh, I should be crying *
* But I just can't let it go *
去死吧
Rot in hell.
SINGER: * Should be hoping  but I can't stop *
* Thinking and thinking  and thinking *
* Of all the things  we should've said *
* That we never said *
* And all the things  we should have done *
* That we never did *
* All the things  that you wanted from me *
我要怎么解释这一切呢
How am I gonna explain this?
旧的不去
You let the old south burn.
新的不来
So something new can rise.
SINGER: * Oh, darling *
* Make it go *
* Just make it go away *
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧、泰剧
离线高清缓存 支持电视投屏
各大应用商店皆可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
扫描即可下载
本视频由哒哒字幕组原创译制
合作请加QQ:2643527418